Guide to the Cornell Law School student records, (ca.1890-1965).
Cornell Law School student records,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell Law School student records, (ca.1890-1965).
18/04/3174
Cornell Law School. Office of the Registrar.
8.5 cubic ft.
Photographs, Printed Materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Student record cards in alphabetical order containing admissions and academic information, including photographs.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Student record cards in alphabetical order containing admissions and academic information, including photographs.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell Law School.; Cornell University -- Students.; Cornell University
Subjects:
Students
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
During student's lifetime individual student records restricted to permission of student and office of origin.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Student Record Cards
CONTAINER LIST
- Student Record Cards, 1890-1965
  - A-Bel, 1890-1965 (Box 1)
  - Belli-Bur, 1890-1965 (Box 2)
  - Bur-Corb, 1890-1965 (Box 3)
  - Corc-Don, 1890-1965 (Box 4)
  - Dor-Flem, 1890-1965 (Box 5)
  - Flex-Got, 1890-1965 (Box 6)
  - Gou-Het, 1890-1965 (Box 7)
  - Hig-Kap, 1890-1965 (Box 8)
  - Kar-Leh, 1890-1965 (Box 9)
  - Leh-Maso, 1890-1965 (Box 10)
  - Mast-Mur, 1890-1965 (Box 11)
  - Mus-Presc, 1890-1965 (Box 12)
  - Prest-R, 1890-1965 (Box 13)
  - Sa-Spenc, 1890-1965 (Box 14)
  - Spen-Ull, 1890-1965 (Box 15)
  - Ulm-Wilm, 1890-1965 (Box 16)
  - Wils-Z, 1890-1965 (Box 17)